Guide to the The Exit Art Archive 1982 - 2011 MSS 343
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Exhibition Files
  - Poverty Pop: The Aesthetics of Necessity [1993.09]: Sales, 1993 - 1994 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Poverty Pop: The Aesthetics of Necessity [1993.09]: Press Clippings, 1993 - 1994 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Mapping Interior Spaces [1993.10]: Invitations, November 17, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Mapping Interior Spaces [1993.10]: Press Release, November 17, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Mapping Interior Spaces [1993.10]: Electronic Arts Intermix Program, November 17, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Mapping Interior Spaces [1993.10]: Attendance/Box Office Report, November 17 - 19, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Mapping Interior Spaces [1993.10]: Press Clipping - The Village Voice, November 23, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Existential / Political: Rudolph Baranik & May Stevens [1994.01]: Invitations, January 29, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Existential / Political: Rudolph Baranik & May Stevens [1994.01]: Invitation Proofs, 1990, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Existential / Political: Rudolph Baranik & May Stevens [1994.01]: Press Release, January 29, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Existential / Political: Rudolph Baranik & May Stevens [1994.01]: Funding - Richard A. Florsheim Art Fund, [1993 - 1994] (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Existential / Political: Rudolph Baranik & May Stevens [1994.01]: Correspondence, 1990, 1992 - 1994 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Existential / Political: Rudolph Baranik & May Stevens [1994.01]: Exhibition Checklist and Price List, January 29, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Existential / Political: Rudolph Baranik & May Stevens [1994.01]: Shipping Information [Art Cart, Inc. Invoices], January 17, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Existential / Political: Rudolph Baranik & May Stevens [1994.01]: Installation Information, January 29, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Existential / Political: Rudolph Baranik & May Stevens [1994.01]: Public Program - The Argument (Panel Discussion), February 17, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Existential / Political: Rudolph Baranik & May Stevens [1994.01]: "In Words" Publication [Drafts, Manuscripts] (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Existential / Political: Rudolph Baranik & May Stevens [1994.01]: Press Clippings, Press Pack (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - All The Love We Lost [1994.02]: Invitations, February 11, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - All the Love We Lost [1994.02]: Press Release, February 11, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - All the Love We Lost [1994.02]: Correspondence (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - All the Love We Lost [1994.02]: Equipment Rental Information (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - All the Love We Lost [1994.02]: Budget/Final Report, February 11, [1994] (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - All the Love We Lost [1994.02]: Max Blagg Drawings, February 11, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - The Garden of Sculptural Delights [1994.03]: Invitations, March 12, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - The Garden of Sculptural Delights [1994.03]: Press Release, March 12, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - The Garden of Sculptural Delights [1994.03]: Exhibition Program (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - The Garden of Sculptural Delights [1994.03]: Exhibition Checklist and Price List (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - The Garden of Sculptural Delights [1994.03]: Loan Information (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - The Garden of Sculptural Delights [1994.03]: Shipping Information (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - The Garden of Sculptural Delights [1994.03]: Installation Information, February 19, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - The Garden of Sculptural Delights [1994.03]: Artist Files (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - The Garden of Sculptural Delights [1994.03]: Correspondence, 1993 - 1994 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - The Garden of Sculptural Delights [1994.03]: Sales/Reserves (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - The Garden of Sculptural Delights [1994.03]: Press Clippings (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Man Trouble [1994.04]: Invitations, April 22, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Man Trouble [1994.04]: Press Clippings, April 22, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Man Trouble [1994.04]: Programs, April 22 - 24, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Man Trouble [1994.04]: Correspondence, 1993 - 1994 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Man Trouble [1994.04]: Film Information (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Man Trouble [1994.04]: Release Forms, April 1994 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Man Trouble [1994.04]: Equipment Rental Information, April 1994 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Man Trouble [1994.04]: Reservations, April 1994 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Man Trouble [1994.04]: Final Report, April 1994 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Conspiracies 1994 [1994.05]: Invitations, June 3, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Conspiracies 1994 [1994.05]: Press Release, June 3, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Conspiracies 1994 [1994.05]: Programs, June 4 - 5, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Conspiracies 1994 [1994.05]: Equipment Information, June 1994 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Conspiracies 1994 [1994.05]: Final Report, June 1994 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Conspiracies 1994 [1994.05]: Press Clipping - "Making the Point Garde" by Amy Taubin for The Village Voice, June 21, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Obscure: Touhami Ennadre and Paul Rosin [1994.06]: Invitations, June 4, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Obscure: Touhami Ennadre and Paul Rosin [1994.06]: Press Release, June 4, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Obscure: Touhami Ennadre and Paul Rosin [1994.06]: Press Listing, June 4, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Obscure: Touhami Ennadre and Paul Rosin [1994.06]: Exhibition Preparation Notes, June 1994 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Obscure: Touhami Ennadre and Paul Rosin [1994.06]: Exhibition Checklist (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - Obscure: Touhami Ennadre and Paul Rosin [1994.06]: Correspondence (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - Obscure: Touhami Ennadre and Paul Rosin [1994.06]: Loan/Shipping Information (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - Obscure: Touhami Ennadre and Paul Rosin [1994.06]: Artist File - Paul Rosin (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - Obscure: Touhami Ennadre and Paul Rosin [1994.06]: Artist File - Touhami Ennadre (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - Obscure: Touhami Ennadre and Paul Rosin [1994.06]: Press Clipping - The Village Voice, June 21, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - The Mouth Inside the Eye [1994.07]: Invitations and Administrative, June 16, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 37)
  - Let the Artist Live! [1994.08]: Invitations, September 17, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Let the Artist Live! [1994.08]: Invitation Proofs (Printing Information) (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Let the Artist Live! [1994.08]: Press Release, September 17, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Let the Artist Live! [1994.08]: Correspondence, 1992, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Let the Artist Live! [1994.08]: Donations (Individuals) (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Let the Artist Live! [1994.08]: Exhibition Checklist, September 17, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Let the Artist Live! [1994.08]: Exhibition Preparation Notes, July - August 1994 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Let the Artist Live! [1994.08]: Internship Postings (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Let the Artist Live! [1994.08]: Exhibition Opening, September 26, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Let the Artist Live! [1994.08]: Artist Lists, July 1994; 2007 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Let the Artist Live! [1994.08]: Artist File - Skip Arnold, 1993 - 1994 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Let the Artist Live! [1994.08]: Artist File - Rachel Feinstein (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Let the Artist Live! [1994.08]: Artist File - Regina Frank (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Let the Artist Live! [1994.08]: Artist File - Paula Hayes (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Let the Artist Live! [1994.08]: Artist File - Kate Howard (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Let the Artist Live! [1994.08]: Artist File - Charles LaBelle, 1992, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Let the Artist Live! [1994.08]: Artist File - Rudy Royval (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Let the Artist Live! [1994.08]: Artist File - Mio Shirai (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Let the Artist Live! [1994.08]: Artist File - Javier Tellez (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Let the Artist Live! [1994.08]: Artist File - Michael Yue Tong (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Let the Artist Live! [1994.08]: Artist File - Trickster Theater Performers (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Let the Artist Live! [1994.08]: Artist File - Ike Ude (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Let the Artist Live! [1994.08]: Artist File - Liz Young, 1993 - 1994 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Let the Artist Live! [1994.08]: Public Programs (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Let the Artist Live! [1994.08]: Papo Colo's Text (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Let the Artist Live! [1994.08]: Press Clippings, 1994 - 1995 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Let the Artist Live! [1994.08]: New York Dance and Performance Award Certificate [Photocopy], September 12, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - It's How You Play the Game [1994.09]: Invitations, November 5, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - It's How You Play the Game [1994.09]: Press Release, November 5, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - It's How You Play the Game [1994.09]: Exhibition Checklist (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - It's How You Play the Game [1994.09]: Biographical Information - Curators (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - It's How You Play the Game [1994.09]: Correspondence - Curators, 1993 - 1995 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - It's How You Play the Game [1994.09]: Correspondence - General, 1994 - 1995 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - It's How You Play the Game [1994.09]: Loan Information, A - H, 1994 - 1995 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - It's How You Play the Game [1994.09]: Loan Information, K - W, 1994 - 1995 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - It's How You Play the Game [1994.09]: Installation and Deinstallation Notes (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - It's How You Play the Game [1994.09]: Press Clippings, 1994 - 1995 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Nora York Concerts [1995.01]: Proposal and Promotion, January 1995 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Research Materials [1 of 2], 1989 - 1999 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Research Materials [2 of 2], 1975 - 1995 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Research Materials (Pieces Not Included in Show), 1992 - 1995 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Curatorial Notes [Black Notebook] (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Invitations, March 4, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Press Release, March 4, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Exhibition Checklist, March 4, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Funding - NEA Final Report (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Loan Forms (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Exhibition Preparation/Installation Information (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Correspondence, 1995 - 1996 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Public Program - Marathon Video Screening, March 24 - 26, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Wall Labels [Cardstock] (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Wall Labels [1 of 5] (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Wall Labels [2 of 5] (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Wall Labels [3 of 5] (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Wall Labels [4 of 5] (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Wall Labels [5 of 5] (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: International Association of Art Critics Award, December 1, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Press Clippings (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Catalogue - Correspondence, 1992 - 1999 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Catalogue - Production Notes (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Catalogue - Essays (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Catalogue - Publication Agreements, 1995, 2001 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Catalogue - Requests/Orders, 1995, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Exhibition Travel - Fact Sheet, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Exhibition Travel - Checklists, [1996] (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Exhibition Travel - Schedule, 1995 - 1997 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Exhibition Travel - Administrative Notes, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Exhibition Travel - Correspondence, 1995 - 1997 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Exhibition Travel - Beaver College Art Gallery, January - February 1996 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Exhibition Travel - Proton ICA (Amsterdam), March - April 1996 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Exhibition Travel - Museum of Contemporary Art (Finland), March - May, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Exhibition Travel - Kulturhusset (Stockholm, Sweden), May - June, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Exhibition Travel - GAK (Bremmer, Germany), May - June, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Exhibition Travel - Gallery 400 (Chicago), November - December, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Exhibition Travel - Miami Dade Community College (Florida), January - February, 1997 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Exhibition Travel - Vancouver Art Gallery (Canada), January - April 1997 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Exhibition Travel - Johnson State College (Vermont), January - March 1998 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Exhibition Travel - Illinois State University Galleries, November - December 1995 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Exhibition Travel - Maine College of Art, September - October 1996 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Exhibition Travel - Wake Forest University, Fine Arts Gallery, October - November 1998 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Exhibition Travel - Galeria Michelle Marxuach (Puerto Rico), September - December 2000 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Exhibition Travel - Leedy-Voulkos Art Center (Kansas City, MO), September - November 2001 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Marina Abramovic (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Vito Acconci (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Bas Jan Ader (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Eleanor Antin (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Skip Arnold (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Judith Barry (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Joseph Beuys (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Chris Burden (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Papo Colo (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Arthur Craven (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Valie Export (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Bob Flanagan and Rose Sheree, 1989, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Sherman Fleming (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Terry Fox (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Gilbert & George, 1991, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Geoffrey Hendricks (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Teching Hsieh, 1979 - 1984 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Kim Jones (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Yves Klein (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Barry LeVa (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Tom Marioni (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Paul McCarthy (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Charlotte Moorman (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Linda M. Montano (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Yoko Ono (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Dennis Oppenheim (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Gina Pane, 1995 - 1996 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Orlan, 1995 -1996 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Pearl (Travis Hutchison), 1994 - 1995 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Rachel Rosenthal (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Carolee Schneeman, 1995 - 1996 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Jill Scott (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Bonnie Sherk (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Barbara Smith (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Stelarc, [1981] (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - Mierle Ukeles, 1984, 1995 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Endurance [1995.02]: Artist File - TR Uthco (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - The Well Video Screening [1995.03]: Proposal and Promotion (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Way Cool [1995.04]: Invitations, May 6, 1995 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Way Cool [1995.04]: Press Release, May 6, 1995 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Way Cool [1995.04]: Studio Visit Schedules, January - February 1995 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Way Cool [1995.04]: Exhibition Checklist, Price List, Preparation Notes, February 1995 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Way Cool [1995.04]: Artist Lists (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Way Cool [1995.04]: Artist Files, A - C (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Way Cool [1995.04]: Artist Files, G - N (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Way Cool [1995.04]: Artist Files, P - Z (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Way Cool [1995.04]: Loan Forms (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Way Cool [1995.04]: Shipping Information (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Way Cool [1995.04]: Public Program - Way Cool Meltdown, July 14, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Way Cool [1995.04]: Sales, Deinstallation Notes (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Way Cool [1995.04]: Press Clippings (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Transfers [1995.05]: Invitations, September 23, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Transfers [1995.05]: Press Release, September 23, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Transfers [1995.05]: Exhibition Checklist and Price List, September 23, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Transfers [1995.05]: Loan Forms (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Transfers [1995.05]: Sales (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Transfers [1995.05]: Correspondence (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Transfers [1995.05]: Artist File - Michael Arvan (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Transfers [1995.05]: Artist File - Drew Beattie and Daniel Davidson (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Transfers [1995.05]: Artist File - Judy Glantzman, 1994 - 1995 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Transfers [1995.05]: Wall Text, September 23, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Transfers [1995.05]: Public Programs - "Imaginary Beings" Performance, November 1995 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Transfers [1995.05]: Press Clippings, October - November 1995 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Nightwalks [1995.06]: Invitations / Announcements, October 1995 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Nightwalks [1995.06]: Press Release, March 1995 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Nightwalks [1995.06]: Schedules, October 1995 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Nightwalks [1995.06]: Performance - Craig Harris & Tailgater's Tales, October 28, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Nightwalks [1995.06]: Performance - Poesing, March 8 - 9, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Nightwalks [1995.06]: Performance - Resonance, May 10 - 25, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - Nightwalks [1995.06]: Performance - Ken Butler & The Gnawa Musicians of Morocco, October 7, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Nightwalks [1995.06]: Press Clippings, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - Sensual Intelligence [1995.07]: Invitations & Project Description, October 8, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - Sensual Intelligence [1995.07]: Correspondence (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Sensual Intelligence [1995.07]: Biographical Information - Composers (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - Sensual Intelligence [1995.07]: Press Clipping - "Control Freaks" by Kyle Gann for The Village Voice, October 31, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - Maya Beiser [1995.08]: Invitations, October 25, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 31)
  - Maya Beiser [1995.08]: Programs, October 25, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 32)
  - Maya Beiser [1995.08]: Correspondence & Administrative (Box 54, Folder 33)
  - Imaginary Beings [1995.09]: Invitations, November 30, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Imaginary Beings [1995.09]: Exhibition Checklist and Price List, December 2, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Imaginary Beings [1995.09]: Press Release, December 2, 1195 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Imaginary Beings [1995.09]: Exhibition Preparation Notes, October 17 - 21, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Imaginary Beings [1995.09]: Correspondence (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Imaginary Beings [1995.09]: Artist Lists (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Imaginary Beings [1995.09]: Artist Files, A - M (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Imaginary Beings [1995.09]: Artist Files, N - Z (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Imaginary Beings [1995.09]: Loan Information, Artists A - G, 1995 - 1996 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Imaginary Beings [1995.09]: Loan Information, Artists H - R, 1995 - 1996 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Imaginary Beings [1995.09]: Loan Information, Artists S - Z, 1995 - 1996 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Imaginary Beings [1995.09]: Wall Text (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Imaginary Beings [1995.09]: Programs - Tricksters, December 9, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Imaginary Beings [1995.09]: Deinstallation Notes / Shipping Information, 1995 - 1996 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Imaginary Beings [1995.09]: Press Clippings, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Counterculture [1996.01]: Invitation Proofs (Printing Information) (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Counterculture [1996.01]: Flyers, February 24, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Counterculture [1996.01]: Press Release, February 24, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Counterculture [1996.01]: Funding - NYSCA, 1994 - 1996 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Counterculture [1996.01]: Funding - NEA, Design Arts Program, 1994 - 1995 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Counterculture [1996.01]: Budget, [1995] (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Counterculture [1996.01]: Guest Curator - Brian Wallis, 1995 - 1996 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Counterculture [1996.01]: Exhibition Consultant - Roz Payne, 1995 - 1996 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Counterculture [1996.01]: Exhibition Consultant - Steven Heller, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Counterculture [1996.01]: Exhibition Checklist, 1995 - 1996 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Counterculture [1996.01]: Installation Materials & Supplies Notes (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Counterculture [1996.01]: Exhibition Wall Text (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Counterculture [1996.01]: Correspondence, 1994 - 1996 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Counterculture [1996.01]: Press Clippings, 1994 - 1996 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Counterculture [1996.01]: Drawing Center, "Cultural Economies" Exhibition, 1995 - 1996 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Counterculture [1996.01]: Research Materials [1 of 2], 1973, 1980, 1982, 1984, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    This folder contains the following:
    Godard, Keith. Glue Glue. Works: New York, NY. 1973.
    Godard, Keith and Emmett Williams. Holdup. Works: New York, NY. 1980.
    Mavrides, Paul and GIlbert Shelton. "The Fabulous Furry Freak Brothers: Burned Again." Rip Off Press, Inc.: Auburn, CA. 1982.
    Mavrides, Paul and GIlbert Shelton. "The Fabulous Furry Freak Brothers: The Idiots Abroad, Part One" Rip Off Press, Inc.: San Francisco, CA. 1984.
    Monk Episode #17. Monk Magazine: New York, NY. 1995.
    Nozone No.2. New York, NY. [undated].
  - Counterculture [1996.01]: Research Materials [2 of 2], 1982, 1985, 1994, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    CLEMegazine, Number 3X. Cle Magazine: Cleveland, OH. 1995.
    The Flue: Sex, Performance, and the 80s. Volume 2, Number 3 Special Summer Issue. Franklin Furnace: New York, NY. 1982.
    PADD and Grass Roots Press, Inc. Countervisions 1985 Calendar. State of Mind, State of the Union Productions: New York, NY. 1985.
    Pinoller: Mental Optimism as a New Life Model, #0. Public Totem Co, Ltd: Moscow, Russia. 1993.
  - Counterculture [1996.01]: Loan Information, Lenders A - H (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Counterculture [1996.01]: Loan Information, Lenders K - M, 1995 - 1996 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Counterculture [1996.01]: Loan Information, Lenders N - P (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Counterculture [1996.01]: Loan Information, Lenders R - S (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Counterculture [1996.01]: Loan Information, Lenders T - W (Box 57, Folder 5)